Guide to the Stephen Rodefer Papers, 1955-1994
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES VIII: AUDIO-VISUAL MATERIALS
  - Subseries: Video Materials
    - Home Movie, "Vagabond Tour", 1947 (16 MM), 3 reels experimental film from student project at SUNY Buffalo, 1966 (Box 35)
    - 3 rolls undeveloped 16mm Kodachrome film, nd, 1 box negatives nd; regular 8 home movies from 1974-1979 (11 reels); 10 reels without labels or dates (Box 36)
    - Rodefer poetry reading 3/17/73 (videotape), Rodefer at Intersection for the Arts, "Influence" 1983 (videotape); "Larry and Jeff Kell reading" nd (video; 2 tapes) (Box 37)
    - "Larry and Jeff Kell reading" nd (video; 1 tape) (Box 38)
  - Subseries: Audiotapes
    - Rodefer message to wife Penny nd (5" reel), unlabeled tape (2 reels; 5" reel); Randall, John Logan, Fields, Harris, and Franks reading at University of New Mexico, 1966 (5" reel); Harris/Goodell reading at Old Town, Albuquerque, NM 1967 (5" reel) (Box 38)
    - "For SF State Poetry Center" by KSAN Radio; asst'd pop classics nd (7" reel; 2 reels), Rodefer music archive, incl. Shepp, Coltrane, Beatles and Montoya nd (7" reel); Larry Goodell/Kenneth Patchen/Ginsberg/Pound recording nd (7" reel) (Box 39)
    - Robert Creeley reading at Berkeley, Jul. 1965 (7" reel), "Young Poets: Coleman, Eichle, Rodefer" Berkeley Poetry Conference, 1965; Basil Bunting reading at Buffalo, NY Jul. 29, 1966 (7" reel); Michael McClure reading at U. of New Mexico, Dec. 6, 1968 (7" reel) (Box 40)
    - The Bell Clerk's Tears Keep Flowing recorded over "The Live Adventures..." (cass.; brief reading; poor sound), Rodefer reading in back yard, Apr., 1977; side B, Safety, 1979 (cass.); Words in Works in Russian: reading Oct., 1979 (cass.); Words in Works in Russian: reading fragment, recorded over "Mark-Almond"(cass.; poor sound); Words in Works in Russian: reading fragment, recorded over "Willow" (cass.; very poor sound); "Steve's Villon" nd; side B, "My Stuff", unidentified jazz recording (cass.); "Villon 142": footnotes; various individual readers, 1980 (cass.); Reading at New College, 1980; reverse, La Pena Music Rehearsal (cass.); Reading at Berkeley with Perelman, 1980 (cass.); Intersection for the Arts: "Influence" lecture and notes (3 cassettes) 1983 (Box 41)